The Hurricane algorithm implementation
version 1.0
(c) by Roman Ganin
2005

Hurricane is the algorithm wich provides the strong 128 (and more) bit data encryption
even better than such fammous algorithms as DES, AES (Rijndael), 3DES, Twofish and others,
and much more faster. This implementation is easy to understand and it can be used to
create file- or socket-relayed secure applications.
The demo is included.